dealstreetasia.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - DealStreetAsia

At DEALSTREETASIA Pte. Limited (“ **Company** ”, “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”), we are committed to respecting the privacy rights of all visitors/users of our website: www.dealstreetasia.com (“ **Website** ”). Through the Website, the Company will provide users with access to a news portal that lists current affairs Content concerning acquisition, restructuring, financing and investment transactions within Asia (“ **Services”** ). As part of the Services, the Company offers some Content on free-basis and limits access to other Content to its subscribers.

Your privacy is important to us and we aim for our Services to be a safe and enjoyable environment for our audience. We respect and safeguard the personally identifiable information (“ **Personal Information** “) we receive and collect from you on our Website and in the course of our other interactions online. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy (“ **Policy** ”) is only applicable to the users of the Website (and its sub-domains), and the information and data gathered therefrom and not to any other website. You are hereby advised to read this Policy carefully and fully understand the nature and purpose of gathering and/or collecting sensitive, personal and other information and the usage, disclosure and sharing of such information. By viewing or accessing the Website and/or subscribing to the Services, you hereby also consent to the Company sharing information with third-party service providers engaged by the Company in relation to its operations and to the transfer and/or storage of Personal Information and data across borders. In addition, your use of the Services shall be subject to the notices, terms, and conditions set forth in this Policy and the Terms and Conditions of Subscription.

Terms not defined herein will have the meaning ascribed to them in the Service Terms and Conditions, as available at [ _Insert Link_ ] (“ **Terms** ”). This Policy shall be deemed and construed to be a part of the Terms. 

This Policy was last modified on March 25, 2018

  * ## **This Policy explains:  **

— The information we may collect about you online;

— The use and role of cookies and similar technologies on our Website;

— How we will protect and use information we collect about and from you;

— The circumstances in which we might disclose your details to anyone else;

— When we may use your details to contact you; and

— How you can be sure the information we hold about you is accurate and current. 

  * ## **Information Gathered**

In general, you can visit our Website without revealing your identity or any Personal Information about yourself. However, you may not be able to access certain areas or Services that require registration, subscription, or need you to reveal your identity and/or other information about you. In particular, you may not access Subscription Services without subscribing to the Services and accepting the Terms. Please note that minors are prohibited from using the Services and the Company is committed to not collecting Personal Information from any minors viewing the Website.

Information that we collect from you may include your username, name, age, email address, place of residence, phone number, and details of transactions you may carry out through the Website. In addition, we may collect demographic information such as information about your computer, location (through GPS), hardware, software, platform, media, Internet Protocol (IP) address and connection, information about online activity such as feature usage and click paths, passwords and other data that you may provide in surveys or online profiles. While we may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, you do not have to mandatorily respond to them. We may combine demographic information with Personal Information to tailor our offerings or web pages, including advertising subject matter, to your preferences or interests. 

  * ## **Personal Information**

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify you and that is not otherwise publicly available, including, but not limited to, your gender, first and last name, email address, phone number, place of residence, password or other contact information. 

We collect Personal Information from you when you register on the Website and subscribe to the Services or otherwise voluntarily chose to contact us and provide such information. When you register with the Website, we will collect certain Personal Information from you in order to provide you with a user account to utilize the Services.

  * ## **Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our web pages and Services may also utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A “cookie” is a small text file that may be used, for example, to collect information about your activity on our Website. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously indicated by you. We use cookies to improve the Website and enable us to offer you superior, more personalised services. Specifically, they enable us to:

— Estimate our audience size and usage pattern;

— Store information about individual preferences, and customise the Website according to individual interests;

— Speed up your searches; 

— Provide you with Content recommendations based on you past searches and article views; and

— Recognise you when you return to our Website.

Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser, but please note that if you choose to erase or block your cookies, you may need to re-enter certain information to gain access to certain parts of the Website. 

Tracking technologies may automatically record information such as Internet domain and host names; other information about your geographic location; IP addresses; browser software and operating system types; CPU type; your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); click paths; dates and times that our Website is accessed; duration of use of our Services, weblogs and other communication data.

Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Website and Services and consequently your experience with the same. We may also analyze information that does not include Personal Information for trends and statistics.

Please note that our advertisers may also use cookies, over which we have no control.

  * ## **Uses of Personal Information**

We may use Personal Information and other information received and collected from you to provide the Services you have requested, including for the purpose of sending you updates or to contact you upon your request and when otherwise necessary. We may also use Personal Information for auditing, research and analysis, and to operate and improve our Services. In certain circumstances, we may share aggregated non-personal information with third parties. In certain limited instances, Personal Information that you provide towards creation of a publicly visible profile on our Website may be indexed by search engines (such as www.google.com and www.bing.com) and may appear in search results on such search engines. 

In the course of using Personnel Information as aforesaid, we may rely on third party service providers and may disclose such Personal Information to such third party service providers. In such cases, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. We may also share such information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and Services. You hereby consent to the disclosure and use of Personal Information in furtherance of the afore-stated purposes.

Unless otherwise agreed, where we propose to use your Personal Information for any other uses we will ensure that we notify you first. You will also be given the opportunity to withhold or withdraw your consent for your use other than as listed above.

  * ## **Confidentiality and Security**

We will keep confidential and protect your Personal Information except where disclosure is required or permitted by law.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Information submitted to us, both during transmission and, once we receive it, for storage and disposal. When you enter sensitive information on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). All information we gather is securely stored within databases controlled by us. The databases are stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

We limit access to Personal Information to employees, agents, advisors and consultants who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or Services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We may provide information, including Personal Information, to third-party service providers to help us deliver our products, information, and Services efficiently and effectively. Service providers are also an important means by which we maintain our Website and mailing lists. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on our behalf through confidentiality agreements and otherwise. We do not intend to transfer Personal Information without your consent to third parties who are not bound to act on our behalf unless such transfer is legally required. Similarly, it is against our policy to sell Personal Information collected online without consent. 

If you choose to provide us with your Personal Information, we may transfer that Personal Information from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world. Your Personal Information may be collected and stored on servers located in the territory of Singapore and any other countries as per our data management policy and practices and our service provider engagements. You hereby consent to the transfer of your Personal Information as aforesaid, and we assure you any such transfer of your Personal Information shall not diminish or adversely affect your rights in relation to such Personal Information as under this Policy.

  * ## **Children’s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect or solicit any information from children below the age of 18 years or knowingly allow such persons to subscribe to our Services. In the event that we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child below the age of 18 years, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child below the age of 18 years, please contact us at _editor@dealstreetasia.com_

  * ## **Third Party Websites**

If you click on a link to a third-party site or otherwise leave the Website, you will go to a website that is outside the purview of our control. Because we cannot control the activities of third parties, we cannot accept responsibility for any use of your Personal Information by such third parties, and we cannot guarantee that they will adhere to the same privacy and security practices as we do. The use of Personal Information by such websites shall be governed by the privacy policies provided therein. Therefore, if you visit a third-party website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that website’s privacy policy before providing any Personal Information

  * ## **Contacting You**

We may contact you using the Personal Information you have given us: 

— In relation to the functioning of any service you have signed up for in order to ensure that we can deliver the Services to you;

— In relation to any transaction entered by you on our Website to subscribe to Services;

— Where you have opted to receive further correspondence;

— Where you have issued a query or requested information from us;

— To invite you to participate in surveys, opinion polls, etc., about our Services or otherwise (participation is always voluntary); and

— To provide you information about our new products and Services.

  * ## **Contacting Us**

Should you have any feedback or enquiries relating to your personal data or if you wish to stop receiving promotional or marketing messages from the Company, please contact:

The Personal Data Protection Officer at the following addresses:

Email: _editor@dealstreetasia.com_

Postal Address: DEALSTREETASIA, Collective Works, 100 Cecil Street, #10-01/02, The Globe, Singapore 069532.

  * ## **Change of Control**

In the event that ownership or control of the Company is to change, your Personal Information may be transferred without notice to you, and you agree to such transfer of your Personal Information. If such a transfer results in a material change in the use of your Personal Information, the Company will provide notice about the choices you have to decline to permit such a transfer.

  * ## **Accuracy**

To the extent that you do provide us with Personal Information, we wish to maintain accurate and current Personal Information and thus ask you to regularly update your Personal Information in case of any change thereof. Where we collect Personal Information from you in the course of providing Services, should you need to update or correct that Personal Information, please contact us and we will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes in your Personal Information that we hold as soon as practicable. You can obtain the information we currently hold on you by emailing the Company at: _editor@dealstreetasia.com_. We will use our best efforts to send you the information within fourteen (14) days of receipt of your email.

  * ## **Consent; Amendments; Law**

By using this Website and the Services, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to our use and management of Personal Information for the purposes and in the manner herein provided. Should this Privacy Policy change, we intend to take every reasonable step to ensure that these changes are brought to your attention by posting all changes prominently on our Website for a reasonable period of time. 

Your visit and any dispute over privacy are subject to this Privacy Policy. The said Policy and the collection, utilization, transfer, disclosure and disposal of Personal Information in connection with the Website shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore, without regard to conflict of law principles. Further, it is irrevocably and unconditionally agreed that the courts of Singapore shall have exclusive jurisdiction to entertain any proceedings in relation to any disputes arising out of the same.
